Guide to the Capitol Hill Restoration Society records, 1904-2012 MS2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Presidents' papers, 1955-1998; MS2009 Series 11; 13.5 Linear feet
  - Larry Pearl: Vertiport, Heliport proposed for and K Streets, NE, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Larry Pearl: Yost House, Master Plan, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Larry Pearl: Zoning Consistency Project -- Ward 6, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Gary Peterson: ABC Board (letter to Harold Brazil), 1994 January 31 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Gary Peterson: Alley Dwelling, 1994 June 26 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Gary Peterson: ANC-6B -- Map, Commissioner Roster, 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Gary Peterson: Architect of the Capitol (re Lee Funeral Home), 1993 September 28 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Gary Peterson: Barney Circle Project, letters, hearings testimony, articles, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Gary Peterson: Blagden Alley (9th & 10th, M & N Streets, NW), 1992 April (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Gary Peterson: Board of Directors (CHRS), 1991 September 23 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Gary Peterson: Bryan Elementary School, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Gary Peterson: Budget Proposed FY, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Gary Peterson: Building Permit Enforcement, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Gary Peterson: Bylaws, (CHRS), undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Gary Peterson: Capitol Hill Achievement Awards, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Gary Peterson: Capitol Hill Hospital, 1995-1995 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Gary Peterson: Capitol Hill Neighborhood Information Center (CHNIC), 1994 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Gary Peterson: Capitol Hill Symposium, May, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Gary Peterson: Capitol Hill Transportation Taskforce, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Gary Peterson: Cartoon Museum (F. Douglas House, 316 A Street, NE), 1993-1994 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Gary Peterson: CATO Institute (National Indian Gaming Association) 24 Second Street, SE, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Gary Peterson: CHAMPS Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Gary Peterson: Children's Island, 1992-1994 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Gary Peterson: Computer Assisted Mass Appraisal (CAMA), property tax assessment program, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Gary Peterson: Cooke Stadium (1), 1993 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Gary Peterson: Cooke Stadium (2), 1993 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Gary Peterson: D.C. Finances, GAO Report, 1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Gary Peterson: Dinner, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Gary Peterson: Eastern Market (1), undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Gary Peterson: Eastern Market (2), undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Gary Peterson: Ellen Wilson Dwellings (1), undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Gary Peterson: Ellen Wilson Dwellings (2), undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Gary Peterson: Environment, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Gary Peterson: F Street, N.E (200 block) opposition to bus route, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Gary Peterson: Fifth Street, N.E. (441), undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (1), undated (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (2), undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (3), undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (4), undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (5), undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Gary Peterson: Historic District (6), undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Gary Peterson: Homicide Report, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Gary Peterson: House Tour (1), 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Gary Peterson: House Tour (2), 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Gary Peterson: Kinney System Parking, undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Gary Peterson: Marion Park, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Gary Peterson: Members List, Alphabetical, 1995 March 01 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Gary Peterson: Members List, by Address, 1995 June 03 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Gary Peterson: Membership Committee, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Gary Peterson: Metropolitan Baptist Church, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Gary Peterson: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Gary Peterson: Newsletter (incomplete), 1992-1993 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Gary Peterson: Newsletter (incomplete), 1994-1995 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Gary Peterson: Nomination Committee, undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Gary Peterson: Planning Committee (1), undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Gary Peterson: Planning Committee (2), undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Gary Peterson: Providence Park, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Gary Peterson: Program Committee, undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Gary Peterson: Publicity, undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Gary Peterson: Public Safety, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Gary Peterson: Safeway, 14th Street, SE, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Gary Peterson: Schools, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Gary Peterson: St. Cecilia's (L C Childcare Center, Little Scholars) (1), 1993 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Gary Peterson: St. Cecilia's (LC Childcare Center, Little Scholars) (2), 1993 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Gary Peterson: St. Cecilia's, Neighborhood Petition, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Gary Peterson: Tax Exemption, Lobbying, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Gary Peterson: Trants Liquors, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Gary Peterson: Treasurer, Tax Returns, 1991-1992 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Gary Peterson: Treasurer, Reports, undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Gary Peterson: Washington Post, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Brad Braden: Architect of the Capitol, re: 321 Mass. Ave., NE, see also 321 Mass. Ave., 1997 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle (1), 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle (2), 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle (3), 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle (4), 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle (5), 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Brad Braden: Barney Circle -- Environmental Assessment, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Brad Braden: Bryan School (1), undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Brad Braden: Capitol Hill Hospital, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Brad Braden: Capitol Hill Rowing Club, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Brad Braden: Capitol Hill Transportation Task Force (1), undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Brad Braden: Capitol Hill Transportation Task Force (2), undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Brad Braden: Capitol Hill Transportation Task Force (3), undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Brad Braden: Children's Island, (not inclusive) (1), 1970-1984 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Brad Braden: Children's Island, (2), 1984-1993 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Brad Braden: Children's Island, (3), 1994-1995 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Brad Braden: Children's Island, (4), 1996-1997 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Brad Braden: CSX Station Place Development, undated (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Brad Braden: Eastern Market, correspondence, announcements, 1997-1998 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Brad Braden: Eastern Market -- Public Space, Exterior Vending (1), undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Brad Braden: Eastern Market -- Public Space, Exterior Vending (2), undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Brad Braden: Eastern Market, testimony, presentations, 1997-1998 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Brad Braden: Eastern Market -- Testimony, Real Property Asset Management & Outdoor Vending Act, undated (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Brad Braden: Ellen Wilson, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Brad Braden: Environmental Issues, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Brad Braden: Garfield Park, renovation and redevelopment, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Brad Braden: Heliport, Helicopter Tours, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Brad Braden: Historic District Committee (1), undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Brad Braden: Historic District Committee (2), undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Brad Braden: House Tour, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Brad Braden: Judiciary Office Center (1), undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Brad Braden: Judiciary Office Center (2), undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Brad Braden: Kentucky Courts, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Brad Braden: 821 Maryland Avenue, proposed shelter (1), undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Brad Braden: 821 Maryland Avenue, proposed shelter (2), undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Brad Braden: 321 Massachusetts Avenue, demolition, (1), 1996-1997 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Brad Braden: 321 Massachusetts Avenue, demolition, (2), 1996-1997 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Brad Braden: 321 Massachusetts Avenue, Proposed Child Care Facility (CHRS vs. Arch. of the Capitol), 1996 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Brad Braden: Membership, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Brad Braden: Metrobus, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Brad Braden: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Brad Braden: Schools, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Brad Braden: Shelters, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Brad Braden: Stadium, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Brad Braden: Trees for the Hill, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Brad Braden: Union Station, Traffic Impact Study (1), undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Brad Braden: Union Station, Traffic Impact Study (2), undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Brad Braden: Union Station, Traffic Impact Study (3), undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Brad Braden: Vacant Lots, Abandoned Vehicles, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Arline Roback papers, 1950-1983; MS2009 Series 12; 1 Linear feet
  This series contains newspaper articles, correspondence, testimony, reports, photographs, and legal documents. This material cover stye years 1950-83. This series includes the personal papers of Arline Roback, a member of CHRS. The series has material for many of the issues Roback worked on during her time with CHRS including Friendship House, Monarch Construction Company scandal, and various organizations including Capitol Hill Defense Fund, Capitol Hill Southeast Citizens Association, and Capital Hill Theatre.
  - Barbara Held Realty Inc., undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Held Realty Inc. -- Newsletters, 1970-1979 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - C Street Development, 1954-1960 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Defense Fund -- Harvest Supper Benefit, 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Hill Defense Fund -- Kennedy Center Benefit, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society, 1958-1983 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Hill Southeast Citizens Association, 1963-1966 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Hill Theatre, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Circle-on-the-Hill October 20, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Cemetery, undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - DC Court of Appeals -- Case 12122 Dubois, 1971-1973 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - DC Court of Appeals -- Case 12122 Dubois, 1977-1979 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - DC Court of Appeals -- Case 11706 Monaco vs. BZA, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - DC Court of Appeals -- Case 12596 and 12650, 1978-1980 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Development of the Central Area West and East of the Capitol (Map), 1959 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - East Capitol Street Public Buildings Development Question and Answer Fact Sheet, 1959 March (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Florida House, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Friendship House, 1953-1975 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Litigation, undated (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Madison Memorial Library, 1961-1970 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Monarch Construction Company Scandal, 1964-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1953 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Newspapers, Miscellaneous Issues, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and Postcards, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Providence Hospital, 1963-1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Senate Office Building Commission, 1954 July 17 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter, 1968 April 18 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Restoration of 639 E St, SE, undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Southeast Civic News November, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Square 764 Zoning Change Debate, 1962-1963 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Testimony of Senator Paul H Douglas on Legislative Appropriations --HR 6868, 1963 June 19 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Urban Renewal Bills, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Standing committees, 1965-1986; MS2009 Series 13; 16.5 Linear feet
  This series contains budget records, minutes, comprehensive plans, legal documents, studies, correspondence, and reports. The material covers the years 1965-86. The series includes the records of the permanent committees of the CHRS. The committees represented in the series include Budget, City Planning, Community Relations, Environment, Fine Arts, Landscaping and Beautification, Membership, Programs and Planning, Transportation, Special Awards, Special Crime, Special Awards, and Zoning. Zoning committee folders include forms, newspaper clippings, correspondence, notes, and general information about specific properties.
  - Budget Committee, 1972-1989 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - City Planning Committee: A & P Supermarket Closure @ 500 Twelfth Street, SE, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - City Planning Committee: Advisory Neighborhood Councils, Testimony, 1971 April (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - City Planning Committee: Anacostia Coordinating Council, Old Anacostia: A Capital Gain, Development Plan Overview, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - City Planning Committee: Bill Board, Sixth & Penn. Ave., SE, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - City Planning Committee: Capitol Hill Defense Fund (for legal fees to fight high rise at 14th and Penn), 1975 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - City Planning Committee: Capitol Hill Historic District, Senate Bill 3941, 1972 August (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - City Planning Committee: Capitol Hill Historic District, Senate Bill 520, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - City Planning Committee: Capitol Hill Hospital, Board of Directors, meetings, financial statement, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - City Planning Committee: Capitol Hill Prospectus, 1967 December (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - City Planning Committee: Children's Island, correspondence, 1985 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - City Planning Committee: Citizens' Planning Coalition, bylaws, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - City Planning Committee: Citizens' Planning Coalition, correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - City Planning Committee: Citizens' Planning Coalition, draft resolution, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - City Planning Committee: Citizens' Planning Coalition, list of Officers, meeting announcements, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - City Planning Committee: Citizens' Planning Coalition, resolution, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - City Planning Committee: City Planning Committee Members, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - City Planning Committee: City Planning Committee Minutes, incomplete, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - City Planning Committee: Committee of 100, Articles of Incorporations, change to By-Laws, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - City Planning Committee: Committee of 100, correspondence, resolutions, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - City Planning Committee: Committee of 100,Membership Meeting, Minutes, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - City Planning Committee: Committee of 100, Trustees Meeting, Minutes, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan (Act 5-112), Adopting the Plan, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, CHRS, letters, testimony, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, District of Columbia Components, Staff Draft, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Federal Employment, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Federal Facilities, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Federal Employment and Federal Facilities, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Place, Downtown Component, Innovative Implementation Techniques for Downtown Washington report by Jerold S. Kayden, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Proposed Land Use Component, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Land Use Component, newspaper clippings, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Maps, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Planning Process, MPO, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Proposed Preservation & Historic Features Element, 1983 March (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Synopsis of the Local Portion of the Comprehensive Plan, O.P.S, March, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Citizen's Guide to Ward Planning, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Data Tables and Maps, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Draft Action Plan for 14th and Potomac, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Draft Action Plan for 14th and Potomac, Transportation Issues, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Economic Development Element, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Generalized Existing Land Use (map), 1980 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, notebook, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - City Planning Committee: Comprehensive Plan, Ward Six, Summary Profile, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - City Planning Committee: Corporation for Community Development, Capitol Hill, Proposed Study, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. A.B.C. Board, opposition to renewal of liquor license, James William Plumb, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Administrative Procedures Act, CHRS, Testimony, undated (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - City Planning Committee: D. C. Council, Authority Over Planning and Zoning, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Council Journal vol. 1 no. 1 -- vol. 2, no. 9, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals No.5929 (Proposed High Rise at 14th and Potomac, SE), Brief for Petitioners, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals No.5929, On Petition for Review, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No.5929, Reply Brief for Petitioners, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 8756 Joint Brief and Interviews, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, (Proposed High Rise at 14th and Potomac, SE), Petitioners' Memorandum, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Affidavit of Martin Klauber, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Brief for Intervenor Graham Building Associates, Inc., undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Brief for Petitioners, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Brief for Respondent, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Joint Petition for Review of Order of Zoning Committee, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Motion for Extension of Time, Jan, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals No. 9130 Petition for Review, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Court of Appeals, No. 9130, Petitioners Motion for Summary Reversal, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Freedom and Information Act CHRS Press Release, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Historic Landmark Implementation Amendments Act, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Historic Preservation Review Board nominations, undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Housing and Economic Development Finance Corporation Act of, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Housing and Economic Development Finance Corporation, Congressional Bill and Report, correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Municipal Planning Office, Brochure, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Municipal Planning Office, Central Washington Transportation and Civic Design Study, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Neighborhood Conservation Resource Center, proposal, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Office of Planning and Development Land Use Assessment Downtown Washington D.C., undated (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Office of Planning and Management, correspondence, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Office of Planning and Management, response to question from Capitol Hill Action Group, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Police Station, First District, 1-D, Fifth and E Streets, SE, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Redevelopment Land Agency, Washington Goes Forward, 1968-1976 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Redevelopment Land Agency, Appraisals/Sales, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Register, rules and regulations of the ABC Board, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission, Case 11444 (1115 Independence Ave., SE as apartment building, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission, Case 70-25, (Square 1045, Density change), 1971 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission, Case 71-14, Square 1045, (High Rise Proposal at 14th and Potomac, 1973 June (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission Case 73-10, Amendment to Provisions of the R-4 to permit development of Flats in Townhouses, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission Case 73-13, Proposed Amendments to the Sectional Development Plan, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission 73-17 Proposed Sectional Development Plan Regulations, testimony, notices, etc., undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - City Planning Committee: D.C. Zoning Commission 73-32, Use of Residential Property by Non-profit institutions (Carnegie Endowment for International Peace), 1973-1974 (Box 88, Folder 4)